James R. "Jim" Dunnam papers, Inclusive: 1982-2011, Bulk: 1996-2010
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1982-2010; 4
  - Topical, 1982-2007; 12
    - Redistricting, 1997-2006, undated; 4
      - Waco Builders, Inc., 1997 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - School Finance, 2000-2004, undated; 5
      - General, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Articles, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Associated Press Survey, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - B-On-Time Student Loan Program, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Discussion Questions, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Education and Economic Revitalization, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Enterprise Fund, 2004 September (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Equal Education Opportunity, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Governor Perry’s School Finance Plan, 2004 April (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - HB 1, 2004 May (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Highly Qualified Teachers, undated (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Homeschools, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - La Vega ISD, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - MALDEF, 2004 April (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Meeting Agenda and Proposals, 2004 July (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - Mexican American Legislative Caucus, Pledge for Prosperity, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - News Articles, 2002-2004 (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - Notes and Information, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 21)
      - Public Schools Voter Survey, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Publications (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 69, Folder 23)
      - Publications (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - State Schools and Hospitals, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Sunset Advisory Commission, undated (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Taxes, 2003-2004 May (Box 69, Folder 27)
      - Texas Education Agency, PEIMS Financial Data, 2000-2001 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Supreme Court of Texas, 1999-2003; 6
      - General, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 29)
      - Appropriations Bill, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 30)
      - Rules of Civil Procedure Proposed Amendments, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Texas Youth Commission, 2000-2007; 7
      - General, 2005-2007 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Comprehensive Integrated Health Care Delivery System, 2007 March (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Conservatorship, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Core Standards for Residential Contract Programs, 2000 March (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Cost Report and Case Management Standards, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Court Reports, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Facility Overview, 2007 March (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Juvenile Advocates, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - News Clippings, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Rehabilitation Plan, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Research, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Residential Standards (1 of 2), 2007 March (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Residential Standards (2 of 2), 2007 March (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Scandal Articles, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Statement of Work Outline, Narrative, and Budget, 2002-2004 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Tort Reform, 2003; 8
      - General (1 of 2), circa 2003 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - General (2 of 2), circa 2003 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Newspapers, 1996-2010; 5
  This series contains copies of newspaper clippings from 1996-2010. The subseries Clippings holds general material about the Texas Legislature, politics, and the state; the subseries Dunnam Articles relates to articles specifically about Jim Dunnam. This series is in good condition.
  - Clippings, 2001-2007; 1
    - General, 2001-2006 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Bingo, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - District 56 Candidates, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Elderly and Disabled Tax Freeze, 2006 May (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Election, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Jeffrey Hibbs vs. Dunnam, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Kip Averitt, 2001-2002 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Redistricting, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - State Funded Contract Lobbyists, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - State Funded Lobbyists Articles, 2006-2007 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Texas Enterprise Fund and Texas Energy Center Clippings, 2004-2007 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Texas Governor Race, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Toll Road, 2002-2006 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Walt Fair Scandal, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - 80th Session, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Dunnam Articles, 1996-2010; 2
    - General, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - General, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - General, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - General, 2006 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - General, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - General, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - General, 2010 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Bipartisanship, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Bremond Press, 2008-2009 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Buffalo Press, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Calvert Tribune, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - “Cost Saving ‘Managed Care’ must not be at expense of right to full proper treatment” from Tiempo, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - “Democrats Make a Stand” in The Texas Observer, 2003 June 6 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Dunnam First Session, 1997 January 15 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - “Dunnam Join Other Democrats in Moving To Restore CHIP’s Funding”, 2007 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Dunnam Moving His District Boundary, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Fall 1997 Report of Texas House District 57 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - “Guide tracks down cash for college” from Waco Tribune-Herald, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Madisonville Meteor, 2007-2008, undated (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Marlin Democrat, 2007-2008 (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Mart Messenger, 2007 April (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - “Meeting costs of crime prevention important” from Tiempo, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - New District 57, 2002 (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Re-election, 2002 October (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Rosebud News, 2007 June (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - Sodomy Law, 2003 (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - Texas Monthly’s “The Best and Worst Legislators of 2001”, 2001 July (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - Tiempo, 2007-2008 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - The Waco Citizen, 2007 April (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Waco Farm and Labor Journal, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Waco Tribune-Herald, 2007-2009 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - “West proclaimed Czech Heritage Capital” from The West News, 1997 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Winter 1997 Report to the People of Texas House District 57 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - 99th Legislature, 1999 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Personal, 2002-2003; 6
  The Personal series holds material about the Texas/Oklahoma Bar Grievance from May 2002-May 2003. This series is in good condition.
  - Texas/Oklahoma Bar Grievance, 2002-2003; 1
    - Administrative, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Amicus Brief, General, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Amicus Brief, Brief of Amici Curiae Texas Legislators, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Attorney Complaint Information, circa 2003 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Formal Notification of the Court, 2003 March 13 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Investigation, Correspondence, 2003 March-April (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Investigation, Documents, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Investigation, Hearings, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Investigation, Signatures, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Roberts, Scott, District Grievance Committee, 2003 August 29 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Roberts, Scott, Grievance Form, 2003 March (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Roberts, Scott, Grievance Information, 2003 April-May (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Roberts, Scott, Hearings, 2003 May-July (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Sasser, Hiram S., III, Grievance Form, 2003 March 17 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Sasser, Hiram S., III, Oklahoma Bar Association, 2003 March-May (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Shackelford, Kelly J., Board of Disciplinary Appeals, 2003 April (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Shackelford, Kelly J., Correspondence, 2003 February-April (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Shackelford, Kelly J., District Grievance Committee, 2003 August 29 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Shackelford, Kelly J., Grievance Form, 2003 March (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Shackelford, Kelly J., Grievance Information, 2003 March-April (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Shackelford, Kelly J., Hearings, 2003 May-July (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - State Bar of Texas, Disciplinary Rules of Professional Conduct & Disciplinary Procedure, 2002 May (Box 72, Folder 29)
- Press Releases, 1997-2010; 7
  This series contains press releases, arranged topically. A few topics of note include awards, the Bosque River, the “Dunnam Report,” education, health, homeowners, gun control, re-election, Sunset Advisory commission, and veterans. This series is in good condition.
  - Awards, 1999 November (Box 72, Folder 30)
  - Bosque River, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 31)
  - Capitol Visit, 1997 March (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Census, 2000 March (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Charity, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Defense Economic Readjustment Zones, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - “The Dunnam Report”, 2002 October 21 (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Education, Charter Schools, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Education, Higher Education, 1997-2001 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Education, Teachers, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Education, PTA, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Flemming Fellows Leadership Institute, 1999 November (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Health, Insurance, 2000 April (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Health, Medication, 2000 March (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Health, West, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Homeowners, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Illegal Gun Control, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Judicial Affairs, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Legal Service, 2000 January (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Little League, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Mexican American Legislative Caucus, 2000 January (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Public Hearing, 1998 May (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Public Programs (Spanish), 2000 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Public Utility Commission, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Re-Election, 1999 December (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Republican Party, 2010 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - State Funded Contract Lobbyists, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Sunset Advisory Commission, undated (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Tax Holiday, 2001 July (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Telemarketing, 2002 January (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Texas IT Academy, 2000 April (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Trains, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Veterans, 2001 May (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Waco Drinking Water, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Water Pollution, 2000 December (Box 73, Folder 28)
- Audio-Visual, 1996-2010, undated; 8
  The Audio-Visual series contains Dunnam’s cassette tapes, CDs, photographs, reel tapes, and VHS tapes. Cassettes include recordings of House Committees. CDs holds, among other topics, Dunnam’s state computer files for the 79th-81st sessions. Photographs consist of Dunnam, his family, House of Representatives members, the Killer Ds, and Governor George W. Bush. Reels relate to Blue Bell Creameries and HEB. The VHS subseries includes charter school news clips, committee hearings, legislative sessions, and a variety of other topics. The Audio-Visual series is in good condition.
  - Cassettes, 1997-2001; 1
    - House Committee on Natural Resources 77th Legislature Tape 1, 2001 March 21 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 1)
    - House Committee on Natural Resources 77th Legislature Tape 2, 2001 March 21 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 2)
    - House Committee on Natural Resources 77th Legislature Tape 3, 2001 March 21 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 3)
    - House Committee on Natural Resources 77th Legislature Tape 4, 2001 March 21 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 4)
    - House Committee on Natural Resources 77th Legislature Tape 5, 2001 March 21 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 5)
    - House Committee on Natural Resources 77th Legislature Tape 6, 2001 March 21 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 6)
    - House Committee on Natural Resources 77th Legislature Tape 7, 2001 March 21 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 7)
    - House Appropriations Committee S/C Education Tape 1, 1997 February 10 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 8)
    - House Appropriations Committee S/C Education Tape 2, 1997 February 10 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 9)
    - House Appropriations Committee S/C Education Tape 3, 1997 February 10 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 10)
    - SBOE Committee on Planning Tape 1, 2001 March 29 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 11)
    - SBOE Committee on Planning Tape 2, 2001 March 29 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 12)
    - SBOE Committee on Planning Tape 3, 2001 March 29 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 13)
    - SBOE Committee on Planning Tape 4, 2001 March 29 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Texas House Insurance Committee Tape 1, 1997 March 3 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Texas House Insurance Committee Tape 2, 1997 March 3 (Box 74OVZ, Folder 16)
  - CDs, undated; 2
    - The Abortion Holocaust, undated (Box 74OVZ, Folder 17)
    - The Homosexual Revolution, undated (Box 74OVZ, Folder 18)
    - Smart, Proud, Respected: Student Success in Charter Schools, undated (Box 74OVZ, Folder 19)
    - State Computer Files Dunnam Folder 79th-81st Sessions and District Folder, undated (Box 74OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Photographs, 1997-2010; 3
    - 77th Legislature, 2001 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Blue Hill Cemetery, 2010 July (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Dunnam Order #5749, undated (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Headshot, c. 1999 (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - The House of Representatives Freshman Class of 1997 (Box 73, Folder 33)
    - Jim Dunnam and Children, Negatives, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - Jim Dunnam and Others, Index Prints, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - Jim Dunnam Headshots Black and White, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - Jim Dunnam Headshots Black and White, undated (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - Jim Dunnam Headshots, 2002 May (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - Jim Dunnam Headshots Negatives, 2000 August (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - Jim Dunnam at Family Gathering, undated (Box 73, Folder 40)
    - Jim Dunnam in Legislature, c. 2001 (Box 73, Folder 41)
    - Jim Dunnam in Legislature, undated (Box 82 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Jim Dunnam and Other Legislators, Signed, undated (Box 73, Folder 42)
    - Jim Dunnam Photo Negatives February-May, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 43)
    - Jim Dunnam Photo Negatives January-May, 1999 (Box 73, Folder 44)
    - Jim Dunnam at Podium, undated (Box 73, Folder 45)
    - Jim Dunnam Speaking with Governor George W. Bush, c. 1999 (Box 73, Folder 46)
    - Jim Dunnam in Texas Legislature, undated (Box 73, Folder 47)
    - Jim Dunnam with Three Men, undated (Box 73, Folder 48)
    - Jim Dunnam with Two Men and Woman, undated (Box 73, Folder 49)
    - Jim Dunnam with Wife and Daughter, undated (Box 73, Folder 50)
    - Killer Ds, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 51)
    - Ladies Posing by Car, undated (Box 73, Folder 52)
    - Legett Family Photo, undated (Box 73, Folder 53)
    - Representatives in the Democratic Convention, c. 2001-2004 (Box 73, Folder 54)
  - Reels, 1989-1990; 4
    - Blue Bell Creameries “Texas Musicians”, 1989 July 6 (Box 80OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Parker and Wood, HEB, 1990 May 15 (Box 80OVZ, Folder 3)
  - VHS, 1996-2004, undated; 5
    - Prepared Table Charter School News Clips (1 of 7), 2000 November- 2001 February (Box 75OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Prepared Table Charter School News Clips (2 of 7), 2000 November- 2001 February (Box 75OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Prepared Table Charter School News Clips (3 of 7), 2000 November- 2001 February (Box 75OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Prepared Table Charter School News Clips (4 of 7), 2000 November- 2001 February (Box 75OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Prepared Table Charter School News Clips (5 of 7), 2000 November- 2001 February (Box 75OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Prepared Table Charter School News Clips (6 of 7), 2000 November- 2001 February (Box 75OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Prepared Table Charter School News Clips (7 of 7), 2000 November- 2001 February (Box 75OVZ, Folder 7)
    - House Natural Resources Committee Hearing Tape 1, 2001 March 21 (Box 75OVZ, Folder 8)
    - North Bosque River CAFOs, 1996 October 23 (Box 75OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Deadly Weapons and Machine Gun Magic, undated (Box 75OVZ, Folder 10)
    - TNRCC Public Hearing TMDL in North Bosque, 2000 October 23 (Box 75OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Waco Center for Youth "Autograph Auction", 2001 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 1384, 2001 May 3-4 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 1384, 2001 May 3-4 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Graduation Speech, 2002 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 4)
    - KDFW Fox 4 News "ParoleEL Out of Control" - Becky Oliver, Joe Ellis, Donna Ressl, Phil Fleming, 2004 November 16 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Texas Department of Criminal Justice Legislative Workshop, 2002 March 8 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Stellar I, undated (Box 76OVZ, Folder 7)
    - At It Again, 1996 November 21 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Mayors' Alliance on Water Dr. Jeff Griffith, 2001 March 29 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 9)
    - State of the State, undated (Box 76OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Life "In the Womb" via 4-D ultrasound images. National Geographic Channel, 2005 May 8 (Box 76OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 by Rep. Dunnam & Portion of Committee on Natural Resources (1 of 4), 2001 March 21-April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 by Rep. Dunnam & Portion of Committee on Natural Resources (2 of 4), 2001 March 21-April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 by Rep. Dunnam & Portion of Committee on Natural Resources (3 of 4), 2001 March 21-April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 by Rep. Dunnam & Portion of Committee on Natural Resources (4 of 4), 2001 March 21-April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 & 54 (1 of 8), 2001 April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 & 54 (2 of 8), 2001 April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 & 54 (3 of 8), 2001 April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 & 54 (4 of 8), 2001 April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 & 54 (5 of 8), 2001 April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 & 54 (6 of 8), 2001 April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 & 54 (7 of 8), 2001 April 19 (Box 77OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Texas House of Representatives 77th Legislature HB 2912 Amendment 53 & 54 (8 of 8), 2001 April 19 (Box 78OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Texas House of Representatives 78th Legislature Rep. Jim Dunnam on HB 4 Amendment 52, Against HB 4, and Against HJR 3, 2003 March 19-28 (Box 78OVZ, Folder 2)
    - "Partnership For A Competitive Texas" "Question" & "Waco/Temple", undated (Box 78OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Erath County Property Owners Interviews, undated (Box 78OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Uniquely Texas: A Lone Star Look At Culture & Heritage Tourism, undated (Box 78OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Reading, Writing and Rap, undated (Box 78OVZ, Folder 6)
    - House Natural Resource Committee Hearing Tape 2, 2001 March 21 (Box 78OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Project Alert (Promotional Tape), 2000 December (Box 78OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Texas Moratorium: Balancing the Scales, undated (Box 78OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Texas PSA, 2001 November (Box 78OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Charles Markham - Personal Statement on Impacted Stream, undated (Box 78OVZ, Folder 11)
    - "We The People Muster & Speak", 2001 March 28 (Box 79OVZ, Folder 1)
    - North Bosque River, 2001 March 26 (Box 79OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Howard Dean: Saltillo Plaza - Austin, TX, 2003 June 9 (Box 79OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Press Conference: Kids Cuts - Healthcare, 2003 March 3 (Box 79OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Midwest: Partnership for a Competitive Texas, undated (Box 79OVZ, Folder 5)
    - "Wondering how easy it is for teens to purchase alcohol online? Watch and find out.", undated (Box 79OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Interviews with Beaman Floyd of TCAIS and Dr. Phil O'Connor, National Insurance Expert, 2003 January (Box 79OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Candidate Forum (SGA), 1996 October 23 (Box 79OVZ, Folder 8)
    - “Seinfeld (only)”, undated (Box 79OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 79OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 79OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Untitled, circa 2000 (Box 80 OVZ, Folder 1)